<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<PatientMatching>
<TEXT><![CDATA[

Record date: 2079-05-12





MERCY CARE CENTER
Mercy Internal Medicine Associates
8 Newburgh Street
Terrell, AR 72985

Russell, Donna
10418061
05/12/79


Ms. Russell comes in for further evaluation.  She has been in Rhode Island for 
six months.  Her complaint is that she has heaviness in the chest.  She 
does not have any palpitations.  She does not note that this is 
associated with exertion.  She does have diaphoresis associated with it.  
She does not have any shortness of breath.  This heaviness has been in 
her chest on and off for the last six weeks.  She is quite concerned.

She has a history of hypothyroidism and hypertension.  She also has 
hyperlipidemia and is being treated with Lipitor.  Her health 
maintenance has been in order.  She has just had a hysterectomy.  She 
needs to have a follow-up mammogram done.  However, today I am most 
concerned about her chest heaviness.

PHYSICAL EXAMINATION:  Her blood pressure is 130/80, respiratory rate is 
20 and pulse is 68.  Neck is supple.  There is no lymphadenopathy.  
Chest is clear to both percussion and auscultation.  Cardiac exam is 
regularly regular with no murmurs, gallops or rubs.  Abdomen is soft and 
nontender.  There is no hepatosplenomegaly.  Extremities are clear of 
cyanosis, clubbing and edema.

LABORATORY DATA:  Her sodium is 145, electrolytes are all otherwise 
within normal limits.  TSH is 2.0.  LFTs are pending at this time.  We 
sent her for an electrocardiogram, which showed normal sinus rhythm with 
nonspecific ST-T wave changes.  We also sent her for an exercise 
tolerance test with preliminary reports showing that she went to a 
maximum heart rate of 108, she was on the protocol for 6 minutes 50 
seconds.  She had no evidence of ischemia.

ASSESSMENT AND PLAN:
1.	Chest heaviness.  I am not sure what is causing this.  She may have a 
primary pulmonary problem.  She will be following up with us in one 
week.  It is heartening to see that she does not have an abnormal 
exercise tolerance test.
2.	Hypothyroidism, well controlled at the present time.  Continue same 
dose of Synthroid.
3.	Hypertension, well controlled presently.
4.	Hyperlipidemia.  We will recheck this on her next visit.



RE:  Russell, Donna
MRN #:  10418061
May 12, 2079
Page 2


We will also need to schedule a follow-up mammogram.



_______________________________
Quinn Rutledge, M.D.

QR/QR5
957307.doc
DD:  
05/25/2079
DT:  05/27/2079
DV:  05/12/2079








****************************************************************************************************
Record date: 2079-06-23




MERCY CARE CENTER
Mercy Internal Medicine Associates
18 Newburgh Street
Terrell, AR 72985

Russell, Donna
10418061
06/23/79


HISTORY OF PRESENT ILLNESS:  Ms. Russell is returning for follow 
up.  She has had couple of further episodes of this peculiar 
sensation in which her arm feels like it goes dead and then she 
gets some pressure in her chest.  She gets a slight shortness of 
breath.  It lasts 30 seconds.  She gets as many as three or four 
a day.  The frequency has, however, decreased and she is feeling 
better and better, as she begins to lose some weight.  I think 
weight loss is going to be critical.  She also is less fatigued 
as she begins to lose weight.

Her hypertension has been under better control.  
Hydrochlorothiazide seems to be helping quite a bit in addition 
to the atenolol.

PHYSICAL EXAMINATION:  Blood pressure is 146/86.  Weight has gone 
from 200 to 196 pounds.  Respiratory rate is 20.  Pulse is 64.  
Neck is supple.  There is no lymphadenopathy.  Chest is clear to 
percussion and auscultation.  Cardiac exam is regularly regular 
with no murmurs, gallops or rubs.  Abdomen is soft and nontender.  
There is no hepatosplenomegaly.  Extremities are clear of 
cyanosis, clubbing and edema.

LABORATORY DATA:  Electrolytes are within normal limits.

ASSESSMENT AND PLAN
1.	Hypertension.  Relatively well controlled on 
hydrochlorothiazide plus atenolol.
2.	Weight.  Now began to lose some weight and feeling much 
better as a result of it.
3.	Peculiar chest pressure.  I do not think she has coronary 
artery disease given the exercise test.  In light of this, 
we will try to control her blood pressure and get her to 
lose some weight.  Hopefully, this will help with the 
resolution of her symptoms.



_______________________________
Quinn Rutledge, M.D.

QR/RM5
855930.do
c
DD:  
06/27/2079
DT:  
06/28/2079
DV:  
06/23/2079






****************************************************************************************************
Record date: 2079-08-11




MERCY CARE CENTER
MERCY Internal Medicine Associates
07 Newburgh Street
Terrell, AR  72985

Russell, Donna
10418061
08/11/79


HISTORY OF PRESENT ILLNESS:  Ms. Russell returns for further evaluation.  
She has been doing very well.  She has been exercising and has lost from 
200 to 170 pounds.  She is feeling very well.

Notably, Dr. Lu sent her for a follow-up ETT.  He did not find the 
first ETT acceptable.  The second ETT was grossly positive.  As a result 
of this, I think it is reasonable for us in addition to having her on 
atenolol to stop the hydrochlorothiazide, put her on ramipril and a 
nitrate.  She is having once every two weeks feeling a slight twinge of 
pain that she was having before when she went up steps.

She did have hyperlipidemia.  We have put her on Lipitor, which has 
provided some control.  However, her HCL is still 36 and LDL 118, which 
is not an excellent ratio.  Nonetheless, her CK has been within normal 
limits.

She also has right shoulder lipoma.  This has become apparent since she 
lost so much weight.  She wanted to see someone in follow up and I have 
recommended Dr. Dawson.

PHYSICAL EXAMINATION:  Her weight is 170 pounds, blood pressure is 
120/64, respiratory rate is 20, and pulse is 64.  Neck is supple.  There 
is no lymphadenopathy.  Chest is clear to percussion and auscultation.  
Cardiac exam is regularly regular with no murmurs, gallops, or rubs.  
Abdomen is soft and nontender.  There is no hepatosplenomegaly.  
Extremities are clear of cyanosis, clubbing, and edema.

LABORATORY DATA:  None today.


Russell, Donna
10418061
08/11/79
Page 2


ASSESSMENT AND PLAN:
1.	CAD.  We will start her on ramipril and long acting nitrate.  I also 
gave her nitroglycerine.  We will stop her hydrochlorothiazide but 
continue her atenolol.  She is also on one aspirin a day along with 
Premarin and Synthroid.
2.	Weight loss.  She will continue to exercise.  I suspect she is going 
to lose more weight.  This is excellent.
3.	Coronary artery disease.  Dr. Lu will be deciding when to do a 
cardiac catheterization.  It is his opinion, and I must concur that 
this is an appropriate next step with Ms. Russell.  She is going to 
delay her usual trip to Rhode Island until we can get final assessment 
done on this variety of medical issues.



_______________________________
Quinn Rutledge, M.D.

QR/RM5
055626.doc
DD:  
08/16/2079
DT:  08/18/2079
DV:  08/11/2079






****************************************************************************************************
]]></TEXT>
<TAGS>
<ABDOMINAL met="not met" />
<ADVANCED-CAD met="met" />
<ALCOHOL-ABUSE met="not met" />
<ASP-FOR-MI met="met" />
<CREATININE met="not met" />
<DIETSUPP-2MOS met="not met" />
<DRUG-ABUSE met="not met" />
<ENGLISH met="met" />
<HBA1C met="not met" />
<KETO-1YR met="not met" />
<MAJOR-DIABETES met="not met" />
<MAKES-DECISIONS met="met" />
<MI-6MOS met="not met" />
</TAGS>
</PatientMatching>